jestercade.com 2018-01-15

# Privacy Policy - JesterCade

JesterCade PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy explains what information JesterCade (referred to herein as "JesterCade", "Company", "we", “us”, or “our”) collects from individuals who visit www.JesterCade.com (the "Site"), download the Software (as defined below) and/or participate in the services offered by JesterCade as described herein ("User(s)" or "you"). Please take a moment to review this Privacy Policy, which explains how we use and maintain that information. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you should not visit the Site, download the Software and/or participate in the resources offered by JesterCade.

**Overview and Information Collected**

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through the Site and Software.

We collect two kinds of information through the Site. The first kind is information that can identify you as a specific individual - such as your name and email address (“Personally Identifiable Information” or "PII"). We only collect PII when you have contacted us directly. (See "Collection of Personally Identifiable Information" below). The second kind of information is the kind of non-personally identifiable information ("NPII") collected and stored automatically by many websites. It may include, for example, information about your Internet service provider, operating system, type of browser, geographic location, and pages viewed on the Site. Although this information is related to you, it is not associated with your PII and cannot be linked to you personally.

“Games” include engaging arcade, puzzle, strategy and other video games that are provided free of charge on the Site. Games are offered free of charge via emails sent to you when you sign up on the Site (“Emails”). You can also elect to access Games via push notifications if you agree to receive such push notifications by the Site (“Push Notifications”). In addition, you can download and install the JesterCade software or add-on/extension from the Site (collectively, the "Software"). The Software allows us to display third party applications as well as text link, popup/under, new tab, transitional, shopping and/or banner advertisements based on the web content viewed by that User. No PII is collected through the Software. In addition, the Site and Games may display advertisements from third parties before and/or during gameplay. All third party applications and all advertisements from the Software, Site and Games shall collectively be known as “Third Party Content”.

Your dealings with Third Party Content, including, but not limited to, your interaction with its advertisements and promotions, your clicking on links provided by Third Party Content, purchase of its goods, or any other type of involvement, are solely between you and the third party. Therefore we do not endorse the advertisements, products or other materials of the Third Party Content. If you interact with the Third Party Content, their terms and conditions and privacy policies apply to your rights and obligations with respect to such interaction. Accordingly, such third parties may collect PII or NPII about you.

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**

PII is collected by JesterCade only when you provide it to us via signing up for Emails on the Site and/or the [Contact Us](http://www.jestercade.com/contact) page, in which the Site asks for your name and email address so that you can receive a response to any questions you may have.

If you do not want us to collect your PII as described above or to use and share your PII as described further below in this Policy, you should NOT provide it to us through the Site feature described above. By providing us with your PII using this feature, you are authorizing our use and sharing of your PII as described in this Policy and any subsequent revisions to this Policy that we may publish on the Site.

**Updating Your Personally Identifiable Information.**

If your PII changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, or remove it by emailing our Customer Support at [support@jestercade.com](mailto:support@jestercade.com) or by contacting us using our [Contact Us](http://www.jestercade.com/contact) page.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. In addition, we will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Social Media (Features) and Widgets:**

The Site may include Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on the Site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on the Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Children's Privacy**

Our Site and Software are not directed to persons under 13. We do not knowingly collect PII from anyone under 13 years of age. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with PII we will take steps to remove such information.

**Use and Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information**

We reserve the right to use PII: (1) for the specific purpose for which such information was provided as stated above; (2) for the purposes disclosed at the time such information is provided; and/or (3) as otherwise stated in this Policy.

We do not share, sell or trade any of your PII with any third parties other than described herein. We may share your PII with our principals, employees, consultants, officers, directors, members, agents, subsidiaries, or affiliates, or our parent company and its principals, parent company, employees, officers, consultants, directors, members, agents, subsidiaries, or affiliates (collectively “Related Companies”). Neither we nor our Related Companies contribute to or participate in cooperative databases, which give other companies access to your PII.

We and our Related Companies may provide access to your PII when legally required to do so, to comply with a court order, to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site, Emails, Push Notifications or Software, to limit our legal liability and protect our rights or to protect the rights, property or safety of other users or the public.

We and/or our Related Companies may also disclose your PII to outside companies and consultants that help bring you the services we offer. For example, we and our Related Companies may work with outside companies and consultants to: (a) manage a database of customer information; (b) assist in distributing Emails or Push Notifications; (c) assist with direct marketing and data collection; (d) provide data storage and analysis; (e) provide fraud prevention; (f) provide customer service by phone; and/or (g) provide other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential and maintaining our Site, Emails, Push Notifications and Software. We and our Related Companies require that these outside companies and consultants agree to keep confidential all information we share with them, and use the information only to perform their obligations to us.

In addition, if we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your PII will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified by a prominent notice on the JesterCade home page of any such change in ownership or control of your PII.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

As with many websites, when you visit the Site, it automatically gathers certain NPII based on your computer information and stores it in log files. This type of technical and statistical information is used to customize your experience at the Site, to help us improve the quality of the Site and to make your visits easy, convenient and fun. JesterCade also collects your IP address to help diagnose problems with the Site server and for Site administration purposes.

In addition to the general collection of NPII by the Site (including, but not limited to, IP address, browser type, operating system version, time and date stamp, and landing page), the Software may collect your IP addresses, browser information, operating system information, URLs, HTML, the content of web pages you visit and/or information about your computer, such as installed programs and running processes/services. We may use this NPII to assist us in delivering to you more relevant content in the form of Third Party Content, which appears when you are online generally. We may also work with third party advertising networks and advertisers who help deliver such Third Party Content to you. We may share your NPII and/or aggregated information with our third party partners to improve the relevancy of such Third Party Content and/or to provide other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential. These third party partners, including, but not limited to, advertising networks and advertisers, may also use cookies and other technologies to collect and track NPII such as demographic information, aggregated information, and Internet activity to assist them in delivering Third Party Content that is more relevant to your interests. They may also utilize supplemental data from other sources and analytics methods to help deliver more relevant Third Party Content. However, if at any time, you would like to permanently stop receiving all Third Party Content, you should uninstall the Software, unsubscribe from the Emails and do not use the Site (including via Push Notifications). The directions for uninstalling the Software and disabling Push Notifications are set forth below in the section entitled "Removal."

You can opt-out of the use of your NPII from being used by Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) members. The NAI opt-out tool was developed in conjunction with NAI members for the express purpose of allowing consumers to "opt-out" of the behavioral advertising delivered by NAI members. If you opt-out of the use of your NPII from being used by NAI members, you will continue to receive ads, however, it will prevent NAI members from delivering ads tailored to your preferences and usage patterns. If you opt-out of Interest-Based Advertising (as defined [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/what-is-it)) by one or more NAI member company, that choice will be stored in “opt-out cookies.” If you ever delete opt-out cookies from your browser (such as by clearing all cookies), buy a new computer, or change web browsers, you'll need to renew your opt-out choices. NAI member companies need to be able to read an "opt-out" cookie on your browser to know not to collect and use data for interest-based advertising purposes. For more information or to opt-out click <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>.

**Cookies / Tracking Technologies**

The Site and Software use "cookies" and similar means to collect aggregate Internet traffic statistics and to enhance your experience at the Site and with the Software. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. The Site uses cookies to recognize your preferences and temporarily store session information. This helps to display your customized content and advertising on your later visits to the Site. For example, if you consent to receive Push Notifications via the Site, the Site will use cookies to remember to send you Push Notifications. If you do not want the Site to deploy cookies in your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a website tries to put a cookie in your browser software. You can also manually clear the cookies within your respective browser (for instructions, click [here](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored) for Firefox; [here](https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/32050?hl=en) for Chrome; click [here](https://support.apple.com/kb/ph21411?locale=en_US) for Safari; and [here](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-11) for Internet Explorer). We do not tie any PII to the cookies that we set.

In addition, third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our Site or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 and Flash to collect and store information. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here: 

[**http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118**](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118)

**Third Party Cookies**

The use of cookies by our third party advertisers as well as third party ad servers is not covered by this Privacy Policy (as explained in the NPII section above). We do not have access or control over these cookies. These third parties may use session ID cookies to gather anonymous information.

**Web Beacons**

The Site may contain electronic images known as "web beacons" which are also sometimes called single-pixel gifs. Web beacons may be used to assist in delivering cookies, allow us to count Users who have visited the Site pages and to deliver services via the Site. We may also include web beacons in Emails in order to determine whether such messages have been opened and acted upon. If any partner advertises on the Site, we may work with them to place web beacons on their website to allow JesterCade to collect statistics on how often clicking on those advertisements on the Site results in a purchase or other action on such partner's website. JesterCade may also employ web beacons from third party partners in order to help compile aggregated statistics regarding the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns or other operations of the Site. JesterCade will never allow web beacons on the Site to be used by third parties (other than Related Companies) to collect or access your PII. We do not tie web beacons to any PII you submit while on our Site.

**Use and Sharing of Non-Personally Identifiable Information (NPII)**

We do not share, sell or trade any of your NPII with any third parties other than described herein. We may share your NPII with our Related Companies. Neither we nor our Related Companies contribute to or participate in cooperative databases, which give other companies access to your NPII.

We and our Related Companies may provide access to your NPII to third parties when legally required to do so, to comply with a court order, to allow third party advertising networks to serve you more relevant ads as described above, to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site and/or to limit our legal liability and protect our rights.

We and/or our Related Companies may also disclose your NPII to outside companies and consultants that help bring you the services we offer. For example, we and our Related Companies may work with outside companies and consultants to: (a) manage a database of customer information; (b) assist in distributing Emails or Push Notifications; (c) assist with direct marketing and data collection; (d) provide data storage and analysis; (e) provide fraud prevention; (f) provide customer service by phone; and/or (g) provide other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential and maintaining our Site, Emails, Push Notifications and Software. We and our Related Companies require that these outside companies and consultants agree to keep confidential all information we share with them, and use the information only to perform their obligations to us.

In addition, if we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your NPII will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified by a prominent notice on the JesterCade home page of any such change in ownership or control of your NPII.

**Security**

We have implemented technical, administrative and physical security measures to protect Information from unauthorized access and improper use. We keep information on servers that are protected by firewalls and located in a physically secure facility accessible only to our authorized employees and personnel of the Related Companies. From time to time, we review our security procedures in order to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though, that, despite our reasonable efforts, no security measures are impenetrable and any information transmitted to us or through the Site will be at your own risk.

**Removal**

Users who have downloaded the Software and who do not want their NPII collected as described above should immediately uninstall the Software. You may uninstall the Software by going here [Uninstall](http://www.jestercade.com/deactivate) and following the directions to remove the Software from your computer.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798 entitles California customers to request information concerning whether a business has disclosed Personal Information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. As stated in this Privacy Policy, we will not sell or share your Personal Information with non-affiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes without your consent. California customers who wish to request further information about our compliance with this law or have questions or concerns about our privacy practices and policies may contact us by email at [legal@jestercade.com](mailto:legal@jestercade.com). Please allow 30 days for a response.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy practices, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy or other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Policy, we will notify you here or by means of a notice on the Site’s home page prior to the change becoming effective. You can tell when this Privacy Policy have been last updated by checking the date at the bottom.

**QUESTIONS AND CONCERNS**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy or its implementation, or any general questions, please email us at [support@jestercade.com](mailto:support@jestercade.com). 

Updated: August 4, 2017
